rspca.org.uk 2017-09-04

# Privacy and Cookie Policy | RSPCA

We're committed to respecting your privacy and keeping your personal information safe. This privacy policy tells you what to expect when the Royal Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (RSPCA) collects personal information.

**In particular, this notice tells you about**[ **how we use your information**](https://www.rspca.org.uk/utilities/privacy/information) **and:**

Share this...

  *  Who we are

This privacy notice covers all personal data that is gathered by the Royal Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (RSPCA), charity number 219099.

  *  What personal information we collect about you

We may collect personal information about you. We do not usually collect sensitive personal information about our supporters unless there is a clear reason for doing so.

  *  Children and vulnerable persons

We're committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children and vulnerable people.

  *  Telling us when things change

You can change your mind at any time about how we contact you or ask us to stop contacting you.

  *  Access to your information and correction

We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. 

### How we may use your information

We will not rent, swap or sell your information to other organisations for marketing purposes.

### Cookies

Cookies help us to assess the effectiveness of our website and can provide useful information.

### Telling us when things change

You can change your mind at any time about how we contact you or ask us to stop contacting you.
